Solley mss., 1888-2006 LMC 2885
Lilly Library
- Automobile Catalogs
  - United States
    - Packard, "Packard Twelve for 1937"(SE: 48/1355), (2 copies) (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Custom Cars"(SE: 50/1357), 1938 (Box 15)
    - Packard, "Packard Super–8 1941 One–Sixty..."(SE: 54/1361) (Box 15)
    - Packard, Photographs (see also #1138 – boxed) (Box 15)
    - Packard, Road Tests (Box 15)
    - Packard, Misc. (Box 15)
    - Paige, "Master of the Highway", 1922 (Box 15)
    - Paige, "Paige Six Sixty–Six", 1922 (Box 15)
    - Pathfinder, "King of the Twelves"(SE: 1/680), 1916–1917 (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "Peerless Motor Cars"(SE: 2/334), 1902 (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "Peerless Motor Cars"(SE: 5/337), 1908 (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "All that the Name Implies – 1909 Models" (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "Motor Cars 1910"(SE: 7/339) (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "1910 Motor Cars" (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "Peerless Motor Cars 1912"(SE: 8/340) (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "New Model Peerless '48–Six'"(SE: 9/341), 1914 (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "Peerless"(SE: 10/681), c. 1918 (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "Peerless Motor Car"(SE: 11/682), 1920 (Box 15)
    - Peerless, "Peerless Motor Cars"(SE: 12/683), 1923 (Box 15)
    - Peerless, Misc. (Box 15)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow"(SE: 5/346), 1905 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce Enclosed Cars"(SE: 4/345), 1905 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Great Arrow Motor Cars"(SE: 6/347), 1908 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow The George N. Pierce Company"(SE: 7/348), 1909 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Motor Cars"(SE 8/349), 1910–1911 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Motor Cars", 1912 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Model 38C–2", 1914 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Model 48-B2"(SE: 10/351), 1914 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Series 3"(SE: 11/352), 1915 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Series 4"(SE: 12/685), 1916-1917 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Series Five"(SE: 13/686), 1918 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow 38 and 48 H.P. Models..."(SE: 14/687), 1920 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow"(SE: 15/688), 1921 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Series 33 Dual Valve"(SE: 16/689), 1924 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Series Eighty"(SE: 17/1033), 1927 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow Series 36"(SE: 18/1034), 1928 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow"(SE: 19/1035), 1929 (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "LeBaron Custom Coachwork on Pierce–Arrow..."(SE: 22/1038), 1931 (Mar.) (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Silver Arrow Pierce–Arrow Looks Ahead"(SE: 25/1364), 1933 (Jan.) (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow 1935"(SE: 27/1366) (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, "1937 Pierce–Arrow"(SE: 29/1368) (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, Photographs (Box 16)
    - Pierce–Arrow, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Pontiac, Road Tests (Box 16)
    - Pullman, Photographs (Box 16)
    - Rambler, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Rauch & Lang Electrics, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Reo, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Roamer, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "Rolls–Royce", 1921 (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "Coachwork"(SE: 2/691), 1923 (Nov.) (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 3/692), c. 1924 (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "('Flying Lady') Coachwork"(SE: 4/693), 1925–1926 (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "Advanced Sketches of New Coachwork", c. 1925 (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "Rolls Royce (The New Phantom)"(SE: 5/1040a), 1927 (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "Rolls Royce (The New Phantom)"(SE: 5/1040b), 1928 (Box 16)
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "A New Rolls–Royce..."(SE: 7/1042), 1932 (Box 16)
    - Ruxton, "Enter: the Ruxton"(SE: 3/1045), 1929–1930 (Box 16)
    - Ruxton, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Simplex/Simplex Crane, "Simplex"(SE: 1/360), 1908 (Box 16)
    - Simplex/Simplex Crane, "Simplex Crane"(SE: 7/366), 1915 (Box 16)
    - Simplex/Simplex Crane, Photographs (Box 16)
    - Simplex, Crane, "Body Designs for Simplex Chassis"(SE: 9/695), 1917 (Box 16)
    - Simplex, Crane, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Speedwell, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Stanley, "Stanley", 1916 (Box 16)
    - Stanley, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Stearns/Stearns–Knight, "Stearns – The White Line Radiator...", 1909 (Box 16)
    - Stearns/Stearns–Knight, "Stearns–Knight", 1913 (Box 16)
    - Stearns, "Stearns–Knight"(SE: 1/1046), 1927 (Box 16)
    - Stearns, "The Car of Character..."(SE: 2/1047), 1929–1930 (Box 16)
    - Stearns, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "Stevens–Duryea Automobiles"(SE: 1/370), 1905 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "Stevens–Duryea Automobiles"(SE: 2/371), 1907 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "Stevens–Duryea Limousines"(SE: 3/372), 1907 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "Stevens–Duryea Closed Cars"(SE: 4/373), 1910 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "Stevens–Duryea Motor Cars"(SE: 5/374), 1910–1911 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "Stevens–Duryea Motor Cars"(SE: 6/375), 1913 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "There is No Better"(SE: 7/698), 1922–1923 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, "Stevens Duryea Motor Cars"(SE: 8/699), 1924 (Box 16)
    - Stevens–Duryea, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Stoddard–Dayton, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Studebaker, "Information and Care...Studebaker 1916", c. 1916 (Box 16)
    - Studebaker, "1935 Studebakers" (Box 16)
    - Studebaker, Road Tests (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Stutz"(SE: 1/700), 1917 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "The Car that Made Good in a Day"(SE: 2/701), 1921 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Stutz Special Six"(SE: 3/702), 1924 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "New Safe Body Stutz..."(SE: 5/1048), 1927 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Stutz–Weymann"(SE: 7/1050), 1928 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Custom Bodies by Weymann..."(SE: 8/1051), 1928 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Now a New Series", c. 1928 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Stutz"(SE: 9/1052), 1929 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Safety Stutz, SV–16 and DV–32"(SE: 11/1369), 1933 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Stutz"(SE: 12/1370), c. 1933 (Box 16)
    - Stutz, "Safety Stutz for 1934"(SE: 13/1371) (Box 16)
    - Stutz, Misc. (Box 16)
    - E.R. Thomas Motor Co., "Thomas 'Flyer' Automobiles", 1905 (Box 16)
    - TLC Carrossiers, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Tucker, Misc. (Box 16)
    - American Bicycle Co. (Waverley Electric), "Waverley Electric Vehicles"(SE: 2/45), 1900 (Box 16)
    - American Bicycle Co. (Waverley Electric), Misc. (Box 16)
    - White Co., Photographs (Box 16)
    - White Co., Misc. (Box 16)
    - Wills Sainte Claire, "Wills Sainte Claire"(SE: 1/704), 1924–1925 (Box 16)
    - Wills Sainte Claire, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Willys–Knight, "New Willys–Knight Great Six"(SE: 1/1054a) (photocopy), 1929 (Box 16)
    - Willys–Knight, "1930 Willys–Knight Great Six"(SE: 1/1054b) (Box 16)
    - Willys–Knight, "Model 88", c. 1930 (Box 16)
    - Willys–Knight, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Winton, "Winton Six"(SE: 7/380), 1909 (Box 16)
    - Winton, "48 Winton Six 33"(SE: 10/706), 1918 (Box 16)
    - Winton, "New Winton Six", 1923 (Box 16)
    - Winton, "New Winton Six Sedan", 1923 (Box 16)
    - Winton, Misc. (Box 16)
    - Cadillac, "Color Creations from Nature's Studio", c. 1920s (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac 1928"(SE: 9/946) (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac 12 Cylinders V–12"(SE: 16/953), 1931 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac 16 Cylinders"(SE: 17/954), 1931 (Feb. 15) (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Franklin, "Franklin Custom Coach"(SE: 14/984), 1930 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Graham, "A Truly Modern Motor Car"(SE: 1/986), 1932 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - La Salle, "La Salle"(SE: 2/988), 1927 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Quelques Details sur la Lincoln", 1927 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Story of the Lincoln Body", 1929-1930 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Body Types"(SE: 25/998a), 1930 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Salon Types 1930"(SE: 26/999) (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "The New Lincoln"(SE: 27/1000), 1931 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "New Lincoln Salon Types 1931"(SE: 28/1001) (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln", 1933 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln V-12, 145" (SE: 33/1333), 1933 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "The Lincoln"(SE: 34/1334), 1934 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Zephyr V-12 pour l'Elite", 1937 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, "Lincoln Custom and Continental"(SE: 45/1345a), 1942 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Marmon, "Marmon Cars at the Show"(SE: 5/660a), 1918 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Marmon, "Marmon Cars at the Show"(SE: 5/660b), c. 1918 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Owen Magnetic, "Owen Magnetic"(SE: 3/670), 1919–1920 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "The Packard Eight"(SE: 28/1021a), 1928 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Custom Cars"(SE: 27/1020a), 1927-1928 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Eight Custom 640 Models", 1929 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Eight De Luxe"(SE: 36/1029), 1932 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard for 1938"(SE: 49/1356) (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Pierce-Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow"(SE: 20/1036), 1930 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Pierce-Arrow, "Pierce–Arrow"(SE: 26/1365), 1934 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Pierce-Arrow, "Portraits of the 1936 Pierce–Arrow"(SE: 28/1367) (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Stutz, "Stutz"(SE: 6/1049), 1928 (Box 28 (Oversize))
    - Buick, "Buick Limited"(SE: 8/1312), 1941 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac"(SE: 10/947), 1928 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "New Cadillac V-8 and V-12 and V-16", c. 1930s (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Picture Book of the Cadillac"(SE: 12/949), 1930 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "V16"(SE: 18/955a), 1931 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac"(SE: 19/956), 1932 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac-Fleetwood"(SE: 15/1318), 1936 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Fleetwood"(SE: 27/1320), 1938 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "The New Cadillac Sixteen"(SE: 28/1231), 1938 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Fleetwood"(SE: 30/1323), 1939 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac Fleetwood"(SE: 31/1324), 1940 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Cadillac, "Cadillac... and Cadillac Fleetwood"(SE: 32/1325), 1940 (Sept. 1) (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial"(SE: 6/960), 1929 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Chrysler, "Chrysler Imperial Eight"(SE: 9/963), 1931 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Lafayette, "Lafayette"(SE: 1/632), 1923 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - La Salle, "La Salle"(SE: 3/989), 1930 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Lincoln, Advertisements, c. 1926 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Marmon, "The Marmon Sixteen"(SE: 14/1013), 1932 (Box 31 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Mechanical Specifications of the Packard Deluxe Eight 7-45", c. 1920s (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "A Portfolio of Plates..."(SE: 29/1022), 1929 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Custom Cars"(photocopy), c. 1930s (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Deluxe Eight Models 8–40 and 8–45"(SE: 34/1027), 1931 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Individual Custom Cars"(SE: 32/1025), 1930 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Individual Custom Cars" (scattered photographs), 1930 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Twelve"(SE: 42/1349), 1934 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Where Luxury Reaches..."(SE: 53/1360), 1940 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Senior Cars 1942"(SE: 55/1362) (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Pierce Arrow"(SE: 20/1036), 1930 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Pierce–Arrow, "Two New Twelves"(SE: 23/1039), 1932 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Rolls–Royce of America, Inc., "Rolls-Royce Adaptability"(SE: 6/1041), 1929–1930 (Box 32 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard 6-45 Portfolio"(envelope), c. 1929 (Box 33 (Oversize))
    - Packard, "Packard Motor Company"(envelope), c. 1934 (Box 33 (Oversize))
- Coachwork Catalogs
  - Belgium
    - S. A. Duchatelet, "Rolls–Royce Silver Spirit II", c. 1991 (Box 17)
    - D'Ieteren Freres, "Deux Carrosseries..."(SE: 4/C69), c. 1922 (Box 17)
    - D'Ieteren Freres, "Albert D'Ieteren Carrossier"(SE: 6/C121), 1929–1930 (Box 17)
    - D'Ieteren Freres, "Anciens Etablissements..."(3 gouache renderings), c. 1930 (Box 17)
    - D'Ieteren Freres, Photographs (Box 17)
    - D'Ieteren Freres, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Vandenplas, "Carrosserie Van Den Plas"(SE: 2/C5), c. 1912–1913 (Box 17)
    - Vandenplas, "Carrosserie Van Den Plas"(SE: 4/C51) (includes photocopy), 1919 (Box 17)
    - Vandenplas, "Carrosserie Vanden Plas"(SE: 5/C52), c. 1921 (Box 17)
    - Vandenplas, "Vandenplas s.a."(SE: 6/C122), 1929 (Box 17)
    - Vandenplas, "Carrosserie Vandenplas s.a."(SE: 7/C123), 1930 (Box 17)
    - Vandenplas, "Gouache Rendering Design 8101", c. 1931 (Box 17)
    - Vesters x Neirinck, Photographs (Box 17)
  - Czechoslovakia
    - Sodomka, Photographs (Box 17)
  - France
    - ACB, "Carrosserie ACB", 1948 (Box 17)
    - Antem Carrossier, Renderings, 1948-1949 (Box 17)
    - Antem Carrossier, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Antem Carrossier, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Audineau, "Carrosserie Audineau & Cie."(SE: 1/C7), 1911-1912 (Box 17)
    - Audineau, "La Carrosseserie Francaise, Paul Audineau"(SE: 2/C53), 1924 (Box 17)
    - Audineau, "La Carrosserie Francaise Paul Audineau"(SE: 3/C54), c. 1924 (Box 17)
    - Autobineau, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Baehr, "Pour faire belle…transformable Baehr"(SE: 1/C55), 1924 (Box 17)
    - Baehr, "Pour faire belle…Transformable..."(SE: 2/C56), 1925 (Box 17)
    - Belvallette, "Exposition Universelle de 1900"(photocopy) (Box 17)
    - Belvallette, "Belvallette & Cie"(SE: 1/C8b), 1913–1914 (Box 17)
    - Belvallette, "Belvallette"(SE: 2/C57), 1925–1926 (Box 17)
    - Belvallette, "Offert par Belvallette"(SE: 3/C125), 1927–1928 (Box 17)
    - Belvallette, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Henry Binder, "Henry Binder Paris", c. 1908 (Box 17)
    - Henry Binder, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Henry Binder, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Anciens Etab. Th. Botiaux, "Th. Botiaux"(SE: 1/C9), c. 1906 (Box 17)
    - Anciens Etab. Th. Botiaux, "Anciens Etablissements Th. Botiaux"(SE: 2/C10), 1911–1912 (Box 17)
    - Anciens Etab. Th. Botiaux, "Anciens Etab. Th. Botiaux"(SE: 3/C11), 1913 (Box 17)
    - Broadwater, Paris, "Mettez notre..."(SE: 1/C58), 1926 (Box 17)
    - Generale Automobile, "Carrosserie Generale Automobile"(SE: 1/C12), c. 1913 (Box 17)
    - Henri Chapron, "Packard Henri Chapron Carrossier"(SE: 3/C224), c. 1937 (Box 17)
    - Henri Chapron, "Delahaye 18cv Super–Luxe Diane 3613", c. 1936 (Box 17)
    - Henri Chapron, "Delahaye 135 573...", c. 1950 (Box 17)
    - Henri Chapron, "Delahaye 235 Coupe", c. 1951 (Box 17)
    - Henri Chapron, "Letters – 4 Photographs for Citroen", 1965 (Box 17)
    - Henri Chapron, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Henri Chapron, Misc. (Box 17)
    - X. Chauvet, "Carrosserie X. Chauvet"(SE: 1/C59), 1923 (Box 17)
    - Marcel Chavet, "Marcel Chavet Carrossier"(SE: 1/C126), 1929 (Box 17)
    - R. Cloche, "r. cloche, carrossier"(SE: 1/C60), 1925–1926 (Box 17)
    - Cormouls, "Carrosserie, Cormouls"(SE: 1/C61), 1923–1924 (Box 17)
    - La Carrosserie Nouvelle, "La Carrosserie Nouvelle"(SE: 1/C62), c. 1925 (Box 17)
    - Currus, "Currus Paris"(SE: 1/C63), c. 1922 (Box 17)
    - E. Delalande, "Carrosserie Automobile de Luxe", c. 1905 (Box 17)
    - De Villars, Photographs (Box 17)
    - De Villars, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Driguet Freres, "Les Carrosseries Driguet Freres, Paris", c. 1924 (Box 17)
    - Driguet Freres, "Carrossiers"(SE: 1/C128), 1929–1930 (Box 17)
    - Duvivier, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Facel Metallon, "Bentley Cresta"(photocopy), 1950 (Box 17)
    - Facel Metallon, "Facel Automobile...", 1951 (Box 17)
    - Facel Metallon, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Faget Varnet, "Carrossiers Levallois–Paris", 1947 (Box 17)
    - Fauraux & Cie., "Les Carrosseries des Anciens...Fauraux & Cie.–, c. 1906 (Box 17)
    - Felber Freres, "La Carrosserie Profilee"(SE: 1/C64), c. 1923 (Box 17)
    - Felber Freres, "Magasin de Vente et exposition..."(SE: 3/C129), 1929 (Box 17)
    - Fernandez/Fernandez & Darrin, "Fernandez & Darrin Chrysler 8"(pencil & watercolor rendering), 1936 (Box 17)
    - Fernandez/Fernandez & Darrin, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Fernandez/Fernandez & Darrin, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Figoni & Falaschi, "Figoni & Falaschi"(SE: 1/C226), 1937–1938 (Box 17)
    - Figoni & Falaschi, "Figoni & Falaschi Carrossiers"(SE: 2/C227), 1939 (Box 17)
    - Figoni & Falaschi, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Figoni & Falaschi, Renderings (Box 17)
    - Figoni & Falaschi, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Franay, "Quelques Modeles de Franay"(SE: 1/C66), 1925–1926 (Box 17)
    - Franay, "Franay Carrossier"(SE: 2/C132), c. 1930 (Box 17)
    - Franay, "Cadillac", c. 1938 (Box 17)
    - Franay, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Franay, Renderings (Box 17)
    - Franay, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Jean Gaborit, "Une Carrosserie de..."(SE: 2/C68), 1923 (Box 17)
    - Jean Gaborit, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Galle, "La Ligne Seule Cree L'Elegance"(SE: 2/C134), c. 1929 (Box 17)
    - Galle, "Renderings", c. 1930 (Box 17)
    - Galle, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Gangloff, "Les Applications de brevets..."(SE: 1/C69) (photocopy), c. 1926 (Box 17)
    - Gangloff, "Carrosserie Gangloff, Colmar"(SE: 2/C135b), 1932 (Box 17)
    - Gangloff, "Les Applications de brevets..."(SE: 1/C69) (photocopy), c. 1926 (Box 17)
    - Gangloff, "Carrosserie Gangloff, Colmar"(SE: 2/C135b), 1932 (Box 17)
    - Gangloff, "Carrosserie Gangloff, Colmar"(SE: 3/C228), 1935 (Box 17)
    - Gillotte, "Les Carrosseries de Gillotte"(SE: 1/C70), c. 1924 (Box 17)
    - Gillotte, "Les fils de gaston Gillotte carrossiers"(SE: 2/C136), 1927 (Box 17)
    - Gillotte, "Les fils de gaston Gillotte..."(SE: 3/C137), 1928 (Box 17)
    - Gillotte, "Les fils de Gaston Gillotte Carrossiers"(SE: 4/C138), c. 1930 (Box 17)
    - Gournay Freres, "Les derniers creations..."(SE: 1/C71), 1926 (Box 17)
    - Grummer, "V. Morel Grummer Carrosserie De Luxe"(SE: 1/C72), 1919–1920 (Box 17)
    - Grummer, "Gaston Grummer Carrossier"(SE: 2/C139), 1927 (Box 17)
    - Grummer, "2 Photographs of Aeroprofil Renault", 1934 (Mar. 16) (Box 17)
    - Grummer, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Grummer, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Guillore, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Guettault, "Guettault Carrossiers"(SE: 1/C142), c. 1930 (Box 17)
    - Hibbard & Darrin, "Hibbard & Darrin Paris"(SE: 1/C143) (photocopy), c. 1928 (Box 17)
    - Hibbard & Darrin, "Hibbard & Darrin Coachwork"(SE: 2/C144) (photocopy), c. 1930 (Box 17)
    - Hibbard & Darrin, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Hibbard & Darrin, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Janoir, "La Carrosserie Metallique Janoir", c. 1926 (Box 17)
    - Kellner, "Carrosserie de Luxe et ses Fils Paris"(SE: 4/C16), 1908–1909 (Box 17)
    - Kellner, "Two Hispano–Suiza Photographs", c. 1929, 1930 (Box 17)
    - Kellner, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Kellner, Renderings (Box 17)
    - Kellner, Misc. (Box 17)
    - L. Kremiansky, "Carrosserie Automobile L. Kremiansky"(SE: 1/C73a), 1923 (Box 17)
    - L. Kremiansky, "L. Kremiansky Neuilly – Paris"(SE: 1/C73b), 1924 (Box 17)
    - L. Kremiansky, "L. Kremiansky Neuilly – Paris"(SE: 2/C145), 1928 (Box 17)
    - Henri Labourdette, "Carrossier"(SE: 2/C74), c. 1920 (Box 17)
    - Henri Labourdette, Photographs (Box 17)
    - Henri Labourdette, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Lamplugh, "Carrosserie Automobile..."(SE: 2/C19), 1911 (Box 17)
    - Lamplugh, "Lamplugh"(SE: 3/C20), 1914 (Box 17)
    - Lavocat Marsaud, "Ch. Lavocat Marsaud"(SE: 2/C77), 1925 (Box 17)
    - Lavocat Marsaud, "C. Lavocat Marsaud"(SE: 3/C146), c. 1928 (Box 17)
    - Lavocat Marsaud, Misc. (Box 17)
    - Letourneur & Marchand, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Letourneur & Marchand, Renderings (Box 18)
    - Letourneur & Marchand, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Paul Lucas Carrosserie, "Paul Lucas Carrosserie Automobile", c. 1913 (Box 18)
    - Macquet & Galvier, Renderings (Box 18)
    - Manessius, "Manessius"(SE: 1/C80), c. 1923 (Box 18)
    - Manessius, "Le Carrosseries Manessius"(SE: 2/C147), 1928 (Box 18)
    - Meulemeester Freres, "Carrossiers Ile Robinson A Clichy"(SE: 1/C49), 1931–1932 (Box 18)
    - Million–Guiet, "Champs–Elysees"(SE: 1/C150), c. 1927 (Box 18)
    - Million–Guiet, "Million–Guiet"(SE: 2/C151), 1930–1931 (Box 18)
    - Million–Guiet, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Million–Guiet, Renderings (Box 18)
    - Million–Guiet, Misc. (Box 18)
    - H. Morlet, "H. Morlet"(SE: 1/C81), c. 1925 (Box 18)
    - Muhlbacher, "Muhlbacher"(SE: 1/C21), c. 1910 (Box 18)
    - Muhlbacher, "Petite Histoire de la Carrosserie...Pawlowski"(SE: 2/C152), 1929–1930 (Box 18)
    - Muhlbacher, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Ottin, "Ottin"(SE: 2/C83), c. 1926 (Box 18)
    - Ottin, "Ottin", c. 1925 (Box 18)
    - Ottin, "Ottin"(SE: 3/C153) (photocopy), 1927–1928 (Box 18)
    - Societe Philippon & Cie., "Societe Philippon"(photocopy), c. 1912 (Box 18)
    - Pourtout Carrosserie, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Pourtout Carrosserie, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Maurice Proux, "Maurice Proux Carrossier"(SE: 1/C154), 1929–1930 (Box 18)
    - Maurice Proux, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Rheda, "Carrosserie Automobile la Marque Rheda"(SE: 1/C155), 1928 (Box 18)
    - J. Rothschild & Fils, "J. Rothschild & Fils"(SE: 1/C24), 1911; (2 copies) (Box 18)
    - J. Rothschild & Fils, "Carrosserie J. Rothschild & Fils"(SE: 2/C25), 1912 (Box 18)
    - J. Rothschild & Fils, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Saint–Didier, "Le Transformable Saint–Didier"(SE: 1/C84), 1923 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Salon 1908 – Galeries 1. Stand No. 13"(SE: 1/C27) (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Carrosserie de Luxe"(SE: 2/C28), c. 1914 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "La Transformable"(SE: 3/C85), c. 1923 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Toute la Gamme de Transformables"(SE: 4/C86), 1924 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Toute la Gamme de Transformables"(SE: 5/C87), 1925-1926 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "J. Saoutchik Carrossier"(SE: 7/C157), 1928–1929 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "J. Saoutchik Carrossier"(SE: 8/C158), c. 1929–1930 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Hispano 54 CV"(rendering), 1933–1934 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "J. Saoutchik Carrossier"(SE: 9/C229) (photocopy), 1938 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Cadillac – Drophead Coupe No. 2198", c. 1947 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Talbot Lago Sport Coupe No. 2230", c. 1948 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Talbot Lago–S–Roadster No. 2261", c. 1949 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Talbot Lago Sport Coupe No. 2509", c. 1949 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Talbot Lago Sport Roadster No. 2510", c. 1949 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Talbot Lago Rec. – Coupe No. 2614", c. 1950 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, "Talbot Lago Special Long – No. 2701", 1950 (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, Photographs (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, Renderings (Box 18)
    - J. Saoutchik, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Van Vooren, "Vanvooren"(SE: 1/C159), c. 1928 (Box 18)
    - Van Vooren, "Bugatti – Delage Photographs", c. 1929 (Box 18)
    - Van Vooren, "Carrosserie Vanvooren"(SE: 2/C230), 1937 (Box 18)
    - Van Vooren, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Van Vooren, Renderings (Box 18)
    - Van Vooren, Misc. (Box 18)
    - Vinet, "Ancienne Carrosserie Vinet"(SE: 1/C29), 1914 (Box 18)
    - Van Den Plas, "Le Torpedo – Cabriolet..."(SE: 1/C160), c. 1928 (Box 18)
    - Van Den Plas, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Weymann, "Carrosseries C. T. Weymann"(SE: 1/C161), c. 1927 (Box 18)
    - Weymann, "Carrosseries C. T. Weymann", c. 1928 (Box 18)
  - Germany
    - Binz Karosserie, "Mercedes Benz", c. 1960s (Box 18)
    - Ingenieurbuero Bonnemann, "Bruegge"(SE: 1/C88), c. 1923 (Box 18)
    - Buhne Karosserie, "Deutsche Werkmansarbeit", 1929–1930 (Box 18)
    - Erdmann & Rossi, "Erdmann & Rossi – Jos. Neuss, Berlin"(SE: 2/C233; 3/C234; 4/C235; 5/C236; 5/C237), c. 1933–1939; (15 plates) (Box 18)
    - Erdmann & Rossi, Photographs (Box 18)
    - Glaserkarosserie G.M.B.H., "Karosserie Glaser Dresden"(SE: 1/C89), 1923–1924 (Box 18)
    - Glaserkarosserie G.M.B.H., "2 Fenster Glaser...Mercedes–Benz TYP 500 – Blueprint", c. 1935 (Box 18)